Hello everyone! I'm Mizu Yaegashi, Yua Kudo, and Ai Kusaka from Aozora, the place I've always wanted to see.
We are all three junior high school members, and I'm so glad that so many of you watched our last video.
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun. I was very happy to hear that many of you commented that you went to the "Consignment Party" or "Story Telling Party" and that you watched the video.
This video is titled "A junior high school student member's first undercover visit to a handshake session with a group of faces.
I have never been to a handshake event itself, so this was my real first group handshake event.
So, where are we now?
This is the hall of Tamakiyama.
I am at the venue of today's childcare meeting.
Oosawa, which I wanted to see, to commemorate the release of the 4th single.
We are holding a nationwide free live & group handshake event.
Today, November 24, it will be held at Yama no Hall in Tokyo,
On November 30, it will be held at Osawa Mid in Miyagi, my hometown.
It's been about a year since our 2nd single?
I am looking forward to it.
I wanted to see the nationwide free live & group handshake event in Osawa,
Even if you don't have a prefecture, you can see the free live concert for free.
And for the group handshake event, you only need to have one sword to shake hands with 2 to 3 members of the group,
If you have never been to one of these handshake events, I hope this video will be an opportunity for you to come and meet them.
So today, we, the junior high school students, went to the booth where CDs are sold on the day of the handshake event and bought them,
We, the junior high school students, will go to the booth where CDs are sold on the day of the handshake event and buy them.
Today's lane,
What's that?
Then, this is what it looks like...
Whom will you go to?
Me and YUA will go to one of the lanes.
Oh, right, I'll go to the second lane.
I'm going to be with these two and my sister, Yuria Miyahashi.
I'm going to convey lots of love to them.
Then I'd like to go to this comment akush lane, so...
I would like to go to Toa-chan's place in the comment akush lane.
I want to go to Toa-chan's place. Toa-chan is so kind, I don't think she will crack.
Well, I want to go to Aina Matsunaga's lane (4 points), Shin Yoshimoto's lane, and Emi Sugiura's lane at Comment Akush.
I want to go.
I want to go to all of them.
Now the first group handshake session for the junior high school members is about to start!
I'll do my best!
Boys!
There's a kids' space this time!
It's so cute!
Look, look, look!
Kids space!
Hiragana masks are so cute!
Don't you see the plate I'm going to throw to Ai-chan?
Don't you get it?
This way!
Want to join us?
Let's try this one.
I'm familiar with it.
I don't know.
What do you think?
I did some drawings.
You have a picture book.
Okay, I'm interested in that one.
I'd love to dive in there.
Oh, hands!
That's too much fun!
Okay, okay!
Are you okay? You need the toilet?
I'm on the edge of the toilet!
Come visit us, everyone!
See you there!
We'll see you in full park style after this!
So, that's it!
That's all the music I wanted to see!
Thank you very much!
I'm Sakura. This is Kaeme.
Today, as Sakura,
I'd like to exhibit.
I'm going as Kaeme today.
I'm off.
Introducing Sakura's jumper
Yesterday, I gave Mi-san and her jumper to everyone,
That's right.
You were concerned about it, right?
That's for sure.
But they don't care that much.
They don't care. I don't care.
I'll do my best.
Weakness.
Yeah.
If you were facing me like this, I'm sure I'd know. With your eyes. With your eyes.
Like this, how you look embarrassed. Like you're embarrassed, but you should see it.
Isn't this kind of the point? Don't we open our mouths like this a lot? Sure, I don't know. Tall eyes? High?
Well, thank you very much. Thank you very much. Oh, but higher would be better.
Oh, you don't mind? It's embarrassing. Look at this. You'd prefer it that way? Is it better?
How do you like it? Well, I thought it might give away my neck, so I gave you the manager's number. No, why? No, why? No, why?
It's high. Lower your voice.
Oh, thank you. Thank you very much.
Oh, here we go. I think I lost my voice at the change. It's gone.
It's really good. You're so cute.
I'm from Shizuoka. Just now.
I love it!
I caught a cold.
That's so cool!
You want to go with that? They'll never know.
Yuri, I don't think they'll notice.
Hello, everyone! This is Yamaguchi and...
This is Kichu-Kichu-Ryu.
Seriously, seriously.
Yay!
I'm off!
I've been waiting for you.
Yes, me.
I'm off.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
One more time.
That's good.
Next time.
This video.
We're lined up separately now.
I can see the fans who always come to the show.
I'm so nervous.
That was three.
Lisa, your eyes are a little bit wild and suspicious.
It's a little bit like a wall, but she's just a little bit nervous.
Three pictures, please.
Three?
Three in a row.
Group common?
Group common, yes.
Group common, yes
I didn't put 3 cards.
I'm going to go to Turtle, Yagi and Ivan's lane.
I'm going to go to Ivan's lane.
But I'm going to be found out.
The pattern of being found out by fans and the pattern of being found out by
And the other is when the members find out.
There are two patterns.
I think the probability of being found out by fans before being found out by members
before the members find out.
I'm nervous about that.
I'm on the edge of my seat right now.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Boo-hoo! This time, please.
Nice to meet you.
I want you to put on the cherry blossoms I want you to put on the cherry blossoms I want you to put on the cherry blossoms I want you to put on the cherry blossoms
Thank you very much for your answer.
What?
That's right.
I guess it's obvious right away. What is it?
What is it?
I'm almost there.
Oh, no, water!
Here it comes, here it comes, here it comes!
I'm going to make some sakura...
Boo-hoo! Adammer, I don't mind if you think about it.
I know, I want it!
You're doing it, aren't you?
I was given the nickname "Satchan" by Suzu-chan, who calls me Satchan
And then...
I'd like to go under Yuzu-chan, Ami-chan and Yuzu-chan's names.
I think I'll go with "I want you to know." It's the last one, after all.
I don't know what to do.
It's like this.
Um... Toiwa-chan and...
YUWAN-chan waved to me!
George, today
George licked zy teles today!
Home is just around the corner
Mystery
I'm a teacher, and I've been able to catch a fish.
I'm just getting started, but it hurts.
Hey, this one!
I'll get to it.
Yes Bl mostly also turn day Wait
Bye bye bye
He's too cute.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
It's over.
What's going on?
When we were standing in line...
Yuan and Tomo waved to me.
Really?
They were so cute.
I thought that's how they felt.
It was an emergency.
I got hit.
He's really cute.
Do it.
Oh, man.
He's so cute!
That was fun!
I'm going to the end now if I can get there.
If I go to the end, I can relax.
I'm good at that.
You wanna go?
Go! I can do it!
If we get out of here, they'll know we're here.
Oh, my God, I'm so nervous.
Bye bye!
Main!
Oh, I'm so nervous.
I'll do my best.
Two for the group handshake and one for the individual handshake, please.
One in a row, please.
Good morning.
Good morning
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Cute.
Thank you
Thank you.
It's gone.
There you go.
I'm on it.
Oh, wait, is it turned off?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I made it there in one piece. Oh, my God.
I'm going to Ellen's.
Oh, my God, isn't this amazing?
You're not used to this, are you?
Hey, eteray. Vice principal.
Oh, my God!
Pou dou dou.
Yes, I know.
Thank you! Thank you so much!
Thank you for loving people!
You know?
Elena, what do you like about her?
Her energy.
I'm glad people know how I am.
I'm glad.
I'll continue to be full of energy.
Thank you very much.
Please come again.
Because you didn't turn this off, did you?
Thank you very much.
Which one is it?
Is this your first time at the bar?
Yes, thank you.
What? - What?
What?
Huh?
dru, please pull it out.
Moon Lane...
You look warm.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
You look lovely.
It's adorable.
Warm, warm puffs.
I met him alone in Shizuoka.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye!
Boo hoo. Who said that? We all ran.
That's right.
I don't think she knew. And that's great.
But I think Ellen probably didn't notice at the beginning.
I think this second half is what's coming.
I don't know...
hmm?
mmm
hmm
Hm.
Running is dangerous.
Thanks for the help.
But you know what, maybe... maybe they don't know we're here.
Really?
Ellen and the others probably won't even know it's happening.
What just happened? Why are you running?
The aisle in front of the dressing rooms where the members go.
Oh, that's the way you came?
I was just coming from...
Like these?
They're boots with thick soles.
I'm not used to wearing them.
I couldn't control my momentum on the curve, so I ran into it.
But...
Ellen.
Ai, I think you can do it.
If you've got the courage, Ai.
I'm sure I can make it.
Good luck, Ai!
First of all, don't stare too long.
Look down or turn your eyes away as much as possible.
Yua came to my lane just now.
She looked like she was crying.
I'm going to try not to be recognized like that.
I don't think she'll recognize me because I'm wearing such a disguise.
Okay, that's why I'm going to go to a handshake event for the first time.
I'm going to shake hands with a member for the first time.
I'll start by buying a sword.
Yes, sir.
One for one and two for individual handshakes.
Here we go!
I bought a sword.
See?
I bought it.
I'm going to go now.
Thank you very much.
Oh, my God!
You're so skinny.
I'm fine.
Eat your dinner.
Who's for kids?
Grounded eme
none be avn
chess
250.
Was it too obvious?
It was so easy!
Can Toba see me here already?
What should I do?
Well, I'm off now.
Next time, I'll do my best not to get caught again.
I'm off.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
Hello. What's your name?
What's your name?
I'm Ichigo, and I've been a panhandler for a long time.
I don't know.
I've been told I look a little like Kinoshita.
But...
I guess...
I don't think they know.
The first one...
It's a little too close to my face.
He's wearing a mask.
I'm wearing glasses, and he's looking down at me.
I'm wearing glasses, and they look at me from below.
He told me to eat my dinner.
And that was it.
The second time I saw her...
She said I looked like Kinoshita.
LOL!
I don't think she knew that Towa-chan looked like Kishita.
It was a piece of cake.
May I?
Ouch.
Do you think they'll notice?
I'd like to go to the space now.
I don't know if I can get in without being noticed.
I'm going.
Oh, my God.
Huh.
I'm going in.
No progress.
예
So, I have sneaked into the first group handshake meeting as a junior high school member.
Thank you very much.
That was fun.
How was it, Misa?
I was thrilled.
I was nervous, but it was fun.
I got used to the feelings of the fans, and I think it was a good experience.
How was Yua?
I was nervous, and I tried not to be intimidated, but I think I was a bit nervous.
I tried not to be nervous, but I think I was a little nervous.
But I don't know, I think Ellen didn't notice.
That's great.
How was it, Ai-chan?
What about you, Ai?
Did she find out that I'm a little bit concerned?
Oh, well...
Well, well, well.
This is good, too.
This one's good, too. It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
And, uh, I actually declared it for the kids' space.
What did you think?
Yes, I did.
It was a lot of fun.
Ai-chan became a kid?
I felt like a kid, and we all played together the whole time.
Did you make friends?
Yes!
They were so cute!
I'm so glad!
We only have about 4 months left in junior high school.
I hope we can do various projects while we are in junior high school.
I'm waiting for your comments on what you'd like us to do.
If you have any ideas or suggestions, please leave them in the comments.
You never know, we might even adopt it!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much for your time.
Please subscribe to the Blue Sky channel I've been wanting to watch.
I'm looking forward to your comments.
I'll be waiting for you.
Okay, bye-bye!
I practiced my voice earlier, so I think it'll be okay.
I'll go with this voice.
I'm from Shizuoka Prefecture.
I'm Frog.
I caught a cold yesterday.
Please help me.
It sounds like...